Guide to the Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013.
Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013
- Series I. Articles Submitted for Publication in RRPE
  - Subseries B: Numbered Articles Submitted And Accepted, (originally submitted to specific RRPE issues)
    - #2277b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "The Power of the Machine: Global Inequalities of Economy, Technology and Environment", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 81)
    - #2278b - Reviewed by Bechtold, Brigitte. "Tangled Routes; Women, Work and Globalization on the Tomato Trail", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 82)
    - #2279 - Elveren, Adem. "Social Security Reform in Turkey: A Critical Perspective", 2007 (Box 22, Folder 83)
    - #2280 - Heise, Arne. "The Political Economy of Meritocracy", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 84)
    - #2282 - de Angelis, Massimo. "Globalisation? No Question: Foreign Direct Investment and Labour Commanded", 2007 (Box 22, Folder 85)
    - #2283b - Reviewed by Gabriel, Jackie. "Rebuilding Labor: Organizing and Organizers in the New Union Movement", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 86)
    - #2284b - Reviewed by Hahnel, Robin. "A Critical Rewriting of Global Political Economy", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 87)
    - #2286 - Erbas, Hayriye; Turan, Feryal. "The 2001 Economic Crisis, It's Impacts and Evaluations", 2007 (Box 22, Folder 88)
    - #2287b - Reviewed by Johnstone, Jamie. "You Call This a Democracy?", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 89)
    - #2289b - Reviewed by Munck, Ronaldo. "Globalisation, Poverty and Inequality", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 90)
    - #2290b - Reviewed by Fernandez, Carlos. "Capitalism, Social Privilege and Managerial Ideologies", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 91)
    - #2292b - Reviewed by Patey, Renee. "Transforming Economics; Perspectives on the Critical Realist Project", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 92)
    - #2295b - Reviewed by Vliegenthart, Arjan. "Alternative Models of Transition", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 93)
    - #2296b - Reviewed by Gubert, Laurent. "L'interet Souverain. Essai d'anthropologie Economique Spinoziste", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 94)
    - #2298b - Reviewed by Basole, Amit. "The Eastern Origins of Western Civilization", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 95)
    - #2299b - Reviewed by von Medeazza, Gregor. "Flows of Power", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - #2302b - Reviewed by Nayeri, Kamran. "Sustainable Agriculture and Resistance: Transforming Food Production in Cuba", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - #2304b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "Human Dignity: Social Autonomy and the Critique of Capitalism", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - #2306b - Reviewed by Lidov, David. "Beyond the Promised Land, the Movement and the Myth", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - #2308b - Reviewed by Jackson, Brian. 'The Empire has No Clothes", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - #2309b - Reviewed by Egan, Daniel. "Power and Resistance in the New World Order and Paradigm Lost", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - #2311b - Reviewed by Cato, Molly Scott. "Financial Crisis, Contagion and Containment; Real World Economic Outlook; and The Politics of Money", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - #2313b - Reviewed by Thompson, Frank. "Economic Analysis, Moral Philosophy, and Public Policy", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - #2314b - Reviewed by Veneziani, Roberto. "States and Markets. A Primer in Political Economy", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - #2316b - Reviewed by Barkin, David. "Railroading Economics: The Creation of the Free Market Mythology", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - #2317 - Kotz, David. "Contradictions of Economic Growth in the Neoliberal Era", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - #2319b - Reviewed by Westra, Richard. "Economic Life Beyond Capital", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - #2321b - Reviewed by Enelow, Noah. "Organic Coffee: Sustainable Development", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - #2323b - Reviewed by Oritz, Etelberto. "Introduction to Post-Keynesian Economics", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - #2324b - Reviewed by Veneziani, Roberto. "A Future for Marxism?", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - #2326b - Reviewed by Bradbury, Mathew. "Capitalism Unleashed", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - #2327b - Reviewed by Reati, Angelo. "The Battle on Foundations and its Neglected Issues", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - #2328b - Reviewed by Gabb, Anthony. "The Political Economy of U.S. Militarism", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - #2329 - Goldin, Jaqui. "Knowledge, Agency and Power", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - #2330b - Reviewed by Stanford, Jim. "The State of Working America", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - #2333b - Reviewed by Gabriel, Jackie. "What Workers Want", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - #2334b - Reviewed by Jacobs, Peter. "The Origins of Development Economics: How Schools of Thought Have Addressed Development", 2006 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - #2335b - Reviewed by Salevurakis, John William. "The Global Political Economy of Sex", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - #2336 - Goldstein, Jonathan. "Taking the High Road Only to Arrive at the Low Road", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - #2338b - Reviewed by Rodriguez; Carlos and Heikkila, Riie. "A Quoi Servent les Patrons"", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - #2340b - Reviewed by Leitch, Richard. "Late Victorian Holocausts", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - #2341b - Reviewed by Dugger, William. "Economic Justice andDemocracy", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - #2343b - Reviewed by Liang, Yan. "Reimagining Growth", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - #2344 - Horn, Robert> "Life Among the Subecon", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - #2345b - Reviewed by Lafferty, George. "Institutions, Culture and the Moral Economy", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - #2346 - Montes-Rojas, Gabriel. "Confronting Neoclassical Myths About Self-Employment in Latin America", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - #2349 - Vlachou, Andriana. "Climate Change: The Political Economy of Kyoto Flexible Mechanisms", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - #2351b - Reviewed by Foley, Duncan. "Marxian Reproduction Schema", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - #2354b - Reviewed by Roncolato, Leanne. "Bananeras; Women Transforming the Banana Unions of Latin America", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - #2356b - Reviewed by Newman, Sarah. "Marco-Economics: Making Gender Matter", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - #2358b - Reviewed by Sandilands, Roger. "Knowledge and the Wealth of Nations", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - #2361b - Reviewed by Pepin, Chris. "Downsizing in America: Reality, Causes, and Consequences", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - #2365 - Alam, Shahid. "Bringing Energy Back into the Economy", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - #2368b - Reviewed by O'Hara, Phil. "How Society Makes Itself: The Evolution of Political and Economic Institutions", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - #2369b - Reviewed by Germann, Julian. "Gender Justice, Development and Rights", 2077 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - #2371b - Reviewed by Gezoco. Armagan. "Confessions of an Economic Hit Man", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - #2373b - Reviewed by Skillman, Gil. "Economics in Real Time: A Theoretical Reconstruction", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - #2375 - Moran, Jamie. "How Should We Conceive the Continued Resilience of the US Dollar as a Reserve Currency?", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - #2377 - Jossa, Bruno. "Gramsci and the Labour-Managed Firm", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - #2379b - Reviewed by Beneria, Lourdes. "Amartya Sen's Work and Ideas: A Gender Perspective", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - #2380b - Reviewed by Burkett, Paul. "Socialist Register 2007: Coming to Terms with Nature" (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - #2383b - Reviewed by Gunn, Christopher. "America Beyond Capitalism: Reclaiming Our Wealth, Our Liberty and Our Democracy", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - #2384b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "Financial Crises: Socio-economic Causes and Institutional Contest", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - #2385b - Reviewed by Irving, Dan. "Poor Workers' Unions: Rebuilding from Below", 2009 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - #2386b - Reviewed by Lafferty, George. "Familiar Refrains, Intractable Issues: The Radicalization of Class-Gender-Race", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - #2387b - Reviewed by Joffe, Jerome. "The Global Political Economy of Israel", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - #2388b - Reviewed by Egan, Daniel. "Alternative Theories of the State", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - #2390 - Panayotakis, Costas. "Individual Differences and the Potential Tradeoffs Between the Values of a Participatory Economy", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - #2391b - Reviewed by Lewis, Paul. "Turning to Reality?", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - #2394 - Mendes, Aquilas. "Cuba and the Battle of Ideas", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - #2397b - Reviewed by Roosevelt, Frank. "Capitalism", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - #2398 - Hecht, Jason. "Competition and International Equity Returns: Some Empirical Test of Turbulent Arbitrage", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - #2401b - Reviewed by Heise, Arne. "Inequality and Prosperity: Social Europe versus Liberal America", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - #2403 - Rieu, Dong-Min. "The Fundamental Marxian Theorem in Interpretation of Marxian Value Theory", 20087 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - #2404 - Salevurakis, John. "Islamic Alternatives to Purely Capitalist Modes of Finance", 2009 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - #2408b - Reviewed by Wilson, Tamar Diana. "Racial Competition and Class Solidarity", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - #2409 - Richards, Donald. "Economics and Nature's Standard: Wes Jackson and the Land Institute", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - #2410b - Reviewed by Weisskoph. "Slaves to Fashion", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - #2413 - Bryan, Dick. "Financialization and Marx: Giving Capital and Labor a Financial Makeover", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - #2415b - Reviewed by Fugiero, Melissa. "Fighting for a Living Wage", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - #2418b - Reviewed by Cato, Molly Scott. "Money and Liberation", 2007 (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - #2419b - Reviewed by Musto, Marcello. "The Indiscrete Charm of Incompleteness", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 67)
    - #2421b - Reviewed by Wolff, Richard. "Reclaiming Marx's Capital: A Refutation of the Myth of Inconsistency", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - #2422b - Reviewed by Sinha, Ajit. "Reclaiming Marx's Capital: A Refutation of the Myth of Inconsistency", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - #2423 - Shie, Vincent. "The Rise of Knowledge in Dependency Theory", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - #2428 - Dllery, Thomas. "Post-Keynesian Theories of the Firm Under Financialization", 2009 (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - #2429b - Reviewed by Angotti, Tom. "Socialism for the Twenty-first Century and Cracking US Intervention in Venezuela", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - #2431 - Vasudevan, Ramaa. "From the Gold Standard to the Floating Dollar Standard", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - #2432 - Newman, Susan. "Financialisation and Changes in the Process of Accumulation Along Commodity Chains", 2009 (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - #2433 - Marquetti, Adalmir. "The Profit Rate n Brazil", 2009 (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - #2436b - Reviewed by Leitch, Richard. "Communities Without Borders", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - #2437 - Branco, Manuel Couret; Henriques, Pedro Damiao. "The Political Economy of the Human Right to Water", 2009 (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - #2438b - Reviewed by Elardo, Justin. "Understanding Commodity Cultures", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 78)
    - #2439b - Reviewed by Munck, Ronaldo. "Globalization as the New Imperialism", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 79)
    - #2440b - Reviewed by Leitch, Richard. "Worker Centers", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 80)
    - #2442 - Crotty, James; Lee, Kang-Kook. "Was the IMF-Imposed Economic Regime Change in Korea in the Wake of the 1997 Crisis Justified?", 2008 (Box 23, Folder 81)
    - #2443b - Reviewed by Todorova, Zdravka. "Matrilineal Communities, Patriarchal Realities", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - #2444b - Reviewed by Kaboub, Fadhel. "Class and Labor in Iran", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - #2448 - Brennan, David. "A Tale of Two Thailands", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - #2449b - Reviewed by Ruwanpura, Kanchana. "Capabilities, Freedom, and Equality", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - #2451 - Ioris, Antonio. "The Political Nexus Between Water and Economics in Brazil", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - #2452 - Raman, Ravi. "Transverse Solidarity: Water, Power and Resistance", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - #2454 - Spronk, Susan. "Water and Sanitation Utilities in the Global South", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - #2457b- Reviewed by Canterbury, Dennis. "Multinationals on Trial", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - #2459b - Reviewed by Maier, Mark. "Reintroducing Macroeconomics", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - #2460b - Reviewed by Madi, Maria Alejandra Caporale. "The Challenge of Liberty", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - #2462b - Reviewed by Medina, Marcos R. Aguila. "Worlds in Motion: Theories in Motion?", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - #2463 - Ahlers, Rhodante. "Fixing and Nixing: the Politics of Water Privatization", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - #2464b - Reviewed by Buzgalin, Alexander. "From Soviet Union to Post-Soviet Russia", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - #2465b - Reviewed by Seda-Irizarry, Ian. "New Departures in Marxian Theory", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - #2472 - Dugard, Jackie. "Can Human Rights Transcend the Commercialization of Water in South Africa?", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - #2574b - Reviewed by Sinha, Ajit. "The Economics of Karl Marx Analysis and Application", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - #2475b - Reviewed by Davies, Matt. "Poverty, Work, and Freedom: Political Economy and the Moral Order", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - #2477 - Edvinsson, Rodney. "A Tendency for the Rate of Profit to Fall", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - #2479b - Reviewed by Pimpare, Stephen. "Poverty and Inequality", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - #2480b - Reviewed by Kramer, Brent. "Socialism After Hayek", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - #2482 - Kim, Wonik. "Simultaneous Transitions", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - #2485b - Reviewed by Enelow, Noah. "Fair Trade", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - #2488b - Reviewed by Mongiovi, Gary. "The Structure of Post-Keynesian Economics", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - #2489b - Reviewed by Angotti, Tom. "Rethinking Municipal Privatization", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - #2490b - Reviewed by Emerson, Brian. "A Postcapitalist Politics", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - #2494b - Reviewed by Greenbaum, Joan. "Doubt is Their Product", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - #2495b - Reviewed by Krimerman, Len. "Solidarity Economy: Building Alternatives for People and Planet", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - #2497b - Reviewed by Roberts, Timmons. "Labor-Environmental Coalitions", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - #2498b - Reviewed by Lippit, Victor. "Growth and Development in the Global Political Economy", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - #2499 - Bond, Patrick. "Water, Health, and the Commodification Debate", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - #2502b - Reviewed by King, Mary. "Ex Mex: From Migrants to Immigrants", 2008 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - #2503b - Reviewed by Stockhammer, Englebert. "Money Distribution Conflict and Capital Accumulation", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - #2508b - Reviewed by Perelman, Michael. "Power and Plenty", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - #2511b - Reviewed by Akram-Lodhi, Haroon. "Pro-Poor Land Reform", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - #2512b - Reviewed by Goldstein, Jonathan. "Heterodox Crisis Theory and the Current Global Financial Crisis", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - #2514b - Reviewed by Dugger, William. "Institutions and the Path to the Modern Economy", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - #2515b - Reviewed by Dugger, William. "Economics in the Shadow of Darwin and Marx", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - #2516b - Reviewed by Leitch, Richard. "Labor and the Environmental Movement", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - #2519b - Reviewed by Elitok, Secil Pacaci. "Liberty vs. Power in the Lives of Mexican Amate Painters", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - #2522b- Reviewed by Ramirez, Miguel. "The Confiscation of American Prosperity", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - #2523b - Reviewed by Elitok, Secil Pacaci. "The Costs of Economic Liberalization in Turkey", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - #2524b - Reviewed by O'Hara, Phillip. "Growth and Development in the Global Political Economy", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - #2529b - Reviewed by Ingram, Gordon Brent. "Impasse in Bolivia", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - #2532b - Reviewed by D'Costa, Anthony. "Critical Perspectives on China's Economic Transition", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - #2534 - Yasar, Yavuz. "Gender, Development and Neo-Liberalism", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - #2538b - Reviewed by Marwah, Sanjay. "Locked Out", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - #2539b - Reviewed by Stabile, Donald. "A Measure of Fairness", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - #2541b - Reviewed by Lewycky, Dennis. "The Magna Carta Manifesto", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - #2542b - Reviewed by Basole, Amit. "Internet and Society: Social Theory in the Information Age", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - #2543b - Reviewed by Eres, Benan. "Political Economy and Global Capitalism", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - #2547b - Reviewed by Vernengo, Matias. "The Conscience of a Liberal", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - #2552b - Reviewed by Cohen, Art. "Calling for an End to Second-Class Shitizenship", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - #2558b - Reviewed by Devine, James. "Beyond the World Bank Agenda", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - #2559b - Reviewed by Despain, Hans. "The First Hundred Days", 2009 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - #2568 - Vahabi, Mehrdad. "Soft Budget Constraints and Predatory States", 2010 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - #2577 - Milonakis, Dimitris. "Home Economicus and the Economics of Property Rights", 2011 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - #2601 - Perelman, Michael. "What Went Wrong", 2011 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - #2640 - Saros, Daniel. "The Circulation of Bank Capital and the General Rate of Interest", 2011 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - #2642 - Davis, Ann. "The New Voodoo Economics", 2011 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - #2654 - Panayotakis, Costas. "Theorizing Scarcity: Neoclassical Economics and its Critics", 2012 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - #2667 - Grandados, Jose A. Tapia, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - #2724 - Eres, Benan and Bahce, Serdal. "Competing Paradigms of Competition", 2012 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - #2674 - McIntyre, Richard and Hillard, Michael. "Capitalist Class Agency and the New Deal Order", 2011 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - #2676 - Ivanova, Maria. "Marx, Minsky and the Great Recession", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - #2683 - Basu, Deepankar. "Is There a Tendency for the Rate of Profit to Fall?", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - #2684b - Reviewed by Reati, Angelo. "Theories of Value from Adam Smith to Piero Sraffa", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - A. Sinha. - A response to Reati, 2012 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - #2697b - Reviewed by Richards, Dean. "Liberation Theology Along the Potomac", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - #2698b - Reviewed by Trigo, Yolanda Massieu. "Peasants and Globalization", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - #2700 - Hahnel, Robin. "The Growth Imperative: Beyond Assuming Conclusions", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - #2707b - Reviewed by Pimpare, Stephen. "The Barricades and the Ivory Tower", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - #2709b - Reviewed by Lemus, Blanca. "Nursing and Globalization in the Americas", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - #2710b - Reviewed by Todorova, Zdravka. "The Future of Money", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - #2713b - Reviewed by Enelow, Noah. "Freedom from Want", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - #2716b - Reviewed by Bell, John. "Political Economy and Globalization", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - #2722b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "Technocapitalism: A Critical Perspective on Technological Innovation and Corporatism", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - #2723 - Albuquerque, Eduardo. "Notes on a Crisis", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - #2725b - Reviewed by Frankman, Myron. "Why Doesn't Microfinance Work?", 2011 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - #2727b - Reviewed by Heise, Arne. "Political Economy of Brazil", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - #2731b - Reviewed by Wilson, Tamar Diana. "Globalization and Transformations of Local Socioeconomic Practices", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - #2732b - Reviewed by Xu, Zhun. "Old China's New Economy", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - #2733b - Reviewed by Borowiak, Craig. "Envisioning Real Utopias", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - #2746b - Reviewed by Weeks, John. "A Modern Guide to Keynesian Macroeconomics and Economic Policies", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - #2753b - Reviewed by Lafferty, George. "The Myth Business: Neoliberalism as Ideology", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - #2757b - Reviewed by Friedman, Gerald. "The Future of Union Organising: Building for Tomorrow", 2012 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - ASSA - Frank, Ellen - "The Surprising Resilience of the U.S. Dollar", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - ASSA - Haight, Alan. "Winner Take-A-Hike Markets", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - ASSA - Perelman, Michael. "Intellectual Property Rights and the Commodity Form", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - ASSA - Wolfson, Martin. "Neoliberalism and the Social Structure of Accumulation", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 78)
    - ASSA - McDonough, Terrence. "What Does Long Wave Theory Have to Contribute to the Debate on Globalization?", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 79)
    - ASSA - Crotty, James. "The Neoliberal Paradox", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 80)
    - ASSA - Kotz, David. "Neoliberalism and the SSA Theory of Long-Run Capital Accumulation", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 81)
    - ASSA - Mutari, Ellen. "Radical Political Economy and the State", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 82)
    - ASSA - Weller, Christian. "Worker Rights and Financial Stability", 2003 (Box 33, Folder 83)
    - ASSA - King, Mary. "Women's Work", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 84)
    - ASSA - O'Hara, Phillip. "Chinese Social Structure of Accumulation for Capitalist Long Wave Upswing?", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 85)
    - ASSA - Dumenil, Gerard. "Imperialism in the Neoliberal Era", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 86)
    - ASSA - Crotty, James. "The Effects of Neoliberal Reforms on the Post-Crisis Korean Economy", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 87)
    - ASSA - Koechlin, Tim. "US Multinational Corporations and the Mobility of Productive Capital", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 88)
    - ASSA - Campbell, Al. "The Effect of Neoliberalism on the Fall in the Rate of Profit and Business Cycles", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 89)
    - ASSA - Baiman, Ron. "The Estimated Economic Impact of a Chicago Big Box Living Wage Ordinance", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 90)
    - ASSA - Gunn, Christopher. "Cooperatives and Market Failure", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 91)
    - ASSA - Weller, Christian. "Social Security Privatization and Market Risk", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 92)
    - ASSA - Orr, Doug. "The Rhetoric of the Social Security Debate", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 93)
    - ASSA - Wolfson, Martin. "Neoliberalism and Social Security", 2006 (Box 33, Folder 94)
    - ASSA - Elardo, Justin. "Marx, Marxists, and Economic Anthropology", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 95)
    - ASSA - Grabel, Ilene. "Policy Coherence or Conformance?", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 96)
    - ASSA - Dufour, Mathieu and Orhangazi, Ozgur. "International Financial Crises: Scourge or Blessings in Disguise?", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 97)
    - ASSA - Curtis, Fred. "Is Globalization Dying?", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 98)
    - ASSA - Motiram, Sripad. "Corporate and Cooperative Solutions for the Agrarian Crisis in Developing Countries", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 99)
    - ASSA - Memis, Emel. "A Disaggregate Analysis of Profit Rates in Turkish Manufacturing", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 100)
    - ASSA - Koechlin, Tim. "Fighting Global Poverty, Three Ways", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 101)
    - ASSA - Stockhammer, Engelbert. "Wage Moderation Doesn't Work: Unemployment in Europe", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 102)
    - ASSA - Weller, Christian. "The Benefits of Progressive Taxation in Economic Development", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 103)